<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: javascript | Deivinson Tejeda]]></title>
  <link href="http://deivinsontejeda.github.io/blog/categories/javascript/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://deivinsontejeda.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-12-28T15:58:06-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://deivinsontejeda.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Deivinson Tejeda]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I have learnt EmberJS]]></title>
    <link href="http://deivinsontejeda.github.io/blog/2014/12/28/how-i-have-learnt-emberjs/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-28T11:11:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://deivinsontejeda.github.io/blog/2014/12/28/how-i-have-learnt-emberjs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since two months I come using EmberJS full. We decided to use EmberJS without strong experience and knowledge. We might use another MV<em> JS framework out there, but We are convinced that using a MV</em> JS framework is the right path to follow in order to avoid have a bunch of JS code unmaintainable.</p>

<p>Besides the kind of app we are developing EmberJS made a perfect match for us.</p>

<p>When I&rsquo;m into any technology, I follow closely the info stream about it. Yesterday I read this tweet:</p>

<p><blockquote><p>Looking to use some Christmas money on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/EmberJS?src=hash">#EmberJS</a> learning material. Any recommendations? &#10;&#10;cc: <a href="https://twitter.com/tomdale">@tomdale</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/wycats">@wycats</a></p><footer><strong>@aaronbushnell <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronbushnell/status/548865168080257024">https://twitter.com/aaronbushnell/status/548865168080257024</a></strong></footer></blockquote></p>

<p>That tweet made me think about how I have learnt EmberJS, which is unusual due to way how EmbjerJS is being developed.</p>

<p>EmberJS team core follows an aggressive development strategy until the next release, which consists on <strong>every six weeks a new stable version of EmberJS</strong>.</p>

<p>When you are trying to learn something new for a real project, often you get books, screencast, blog posts and so on in order to ramp up quickly. The problem here EmberJS with its development model tends to get out of date these resources as quick as six-weeks.</p>

<p>So, You can buy amazing books, read incredible tutorials, watch helpful screenshot, but they might going out of date on next release of EmberJS, definitely that&rsquo;s not good. It&rsquo;s very frustrating :&ndash;(.</p>

<p>What we did a custom algorithm to sort out this one in order to get good books for reference and get in touch with <a href="http://emberjs.com/guides/">the official doc</a>.</p>

<p>Might you asking yourself, how works this?</p>

<p>Well, We wanted to have good books with very recent date, in which we get reference to understand more in deep <a href="http://emberjs.com/guides/concepts/core-concepts/">core concepts</a> behind EmberJS and official doc to check out if the book, tutorial, etc is up-to-date. By this way We can take advantage the power of any OSS, its <strong>Community</strong>.</p>

<p>EmberJS is a good framework with amazing community, besides the core team are guys which know a lot of about OSS.</p>

<p>If you are interested on using Ember JS on your projects keep in mind its development life cycle and when you want to buy or read resource check out the release date and version used. There are many projects out there using EmberJS for real and not just tutorials.</p>

<p>We are using it for real and so far so good.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
